Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 37, folder: (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 15: Management Tools For Better Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 16: the Velvet Curtain Show The Power Of The Vote That Is Not Cast, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 17: The Bill Boyntons Go Into Politics, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 18: Educational aids for schools and colleges, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 19: Educational aids for schools and colleges 1955-56, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 20: You and American Competitive Private Enterprise, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 21: Selected NAM Publications Dealing With Employee Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 22: Dear Industrial Relations Executive, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
    By William K. Zinke. August 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: National Conference On mental health And The Business Community, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 24: Settling Complaints in the Non-Unionized Operation, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 25: Can Hiring Halls Replace College Placement Offices?, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
    June 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Special Bibliography of NAM Industrial Relations Publications, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 27: The Bill Boyntons Go Into POLITICS, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 28: Roster of Incumbents 1966, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 29: How To Win Elections!, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 30: the Velvet Curtain Shows The Power Of The Vote That Is Not Cast, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 31: Precinct Power A filmed teaching course in practical politics, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 32: Unemployment Compensation Communications Kit, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 33: Automations and Jobs, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 34: setting safety and health standards by the consensus method, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 35: Incentives and the Welfare Programs, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 36: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 37: For Release In A.M.'s Monday, April 12, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 38: For Release In Morning Papers Of Friday, August 17, 1962, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Box: 37, folder: (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Why Labor Law Reform?, Publication (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: "Labor-Management Responsibilities In A Competitive World", Publication (Box 37, Folder 39)
    December 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: That Taft-Hartley Law!, Publication (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: Labor-Management Relations A Look Ahead, Publication (Box 37, Folder 39)
    By Charles R. Slight, Jr. August. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Industry Looks At Labor-Management Relations Today And Tomorrow, Publication (Box 37, Folder 39)
    By W. P. Gullander. October. Item is in English.
- Box: 37, folder: (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Strengthening Management Teamwork, Publication (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: A Guide To Human Relations Within The Enterprise, Publication (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: Summary Analysis Of Revised Regulations Of The Office Of Federal Contract Compliance, Publication (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: Human and Economic Significance of Healthful Working Conditions, Publication (Box 37, Folder 40)
    By Sybyl S. Patterson. January. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Industrial Relations Policy Statement, Publication (Box 37, Folder 40)
    February 4. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Why Public Affairs, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Policies To Facilitate International Growth, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Automation -- Its Meaning And Impact, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
    By John Diebold. December 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Public Policy and the NAM, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
    By William H. McGaughey. May 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Fact File on Voluntary Unionism one of the important issues affecting the American Economy, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Next Five Years, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: This is NAM, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Public Policy and the NAM, Publication (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Emergency Strikes, Union Power & the Public Interest, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Emergency Strikes, Union Power & the Public Interest, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Government Employee Negotiations & the Public Interest, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Congressional Fellowship Program, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Why Public Affairs, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Compulsory Arbitration Of Industrial Disputes In Foreign Countries, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Dos and Donts for Presenting Congressional Testimony, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The People's Sector, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Richard M. Nixon. April 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Thos unemployment statistics, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: National Association Of Manufacturers Of The United States Of America Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Civic Affairs Study Program, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: A Mini-Report On NAM'S Public Affairs Services, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Statesmanship In Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By LeMuel R. Boulware. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: National Association Of Manufacturers Of The United States Of America Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Employee Understanding of a Free Market Economy, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By L. C. Michelon. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: NAM 1964, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: NAM Second Annual Industrial Relations Workshop, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    October 6-7. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Federal Budget For 1963 Report of the NAM Government Economy Committee, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Do The Seniority Rights Of Employees Survive An Expired Contract?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Eugene A. Hoffman. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Critical Problem Of Financing Unemployment Compensation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Statement of The National Association of Manufacturers, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Statement of the National Association of Manufacturers, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    June 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Case AGAINST Federal Aid to Education, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: National Association Of Manufacturers Of The United States Of America Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Industry Believes 1965 Policies on Current Problems as Adopted by the Board, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Is Compulsory Arbitration The Answer To Labor Conflict?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: Focus On Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Labor Monopolyand Its Implications to a Free Society, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Dr. Leo Wolman. December 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: What Price Compulsory Unionism?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By C. W. Anderson. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: The Productive Years Ages 45-65, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Human Relations And Efficient Production, Publication (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: All Together, Publication (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: NAM's Views On Equal Pay For Equal Work, Publication (Box 38, Folder 3)
    January 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industry's New Dimensions Of Service To Education, Publication (Box 38, Folder 3)
    By WM J. Grede. October. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Responsibilities And Functions Of The NAM Employee Relations Division, Publication (Box 38, Folder 3)
    May 18. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Changing Climate Of Labor Relations, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
    By Charles A. Kothe. May 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: NAM News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: New York Post, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: A Comparison of Three Economic Systems, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The "Primrose Path" Of Centralism, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: What Educators Say About The Program, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Educational aids for schools and colleges, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Our Native Land, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Growth of American Industry, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Creating More JobsNow, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Responsibilities In A Competitive World, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
    By Charles A. Kothe. December. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Emerging Economic Problems Of The 1960's, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 35 years serving the graphic arts industry, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Career and Job Opportunities in the Printing Ink Industry, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report Of The Special Committee To Study Railroad Problems, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Yes - What's the real story about railroad passenger service?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Report Of The Special Committee To Study Railroad Problems, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: NARFE Guardian Of Independent Federal Retirement, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
    August 29. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Present Is Prologue, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    By J. Lloyd Trump, Lois S. Karasik. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: National Association Of Suggestions Systems, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Employee's Suggestion Record, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: The Suggestion Plan A Brief Review of Operating Principles and Procedures, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Gimme The Cash - Let The Benefits Go!, Publication (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Nabisco, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: 1961 Annual Report National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: 1965 Annual Report National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Nabisco Suggestion System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: you'll Find Quality In Our Corner, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Annual Report National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 14: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 17: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 18: 1964 Annual Report National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: 1966 Annual Report National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 20: National Biscuit Company Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment (Exclude Sales Positions), Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Application For Employment And Personnel Folder, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Welcome to Nabisco, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Personnel Relations Department, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Personnel Requisition, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Absenteeism Record, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Change In Pay Roll, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Change In Pay Roll, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Careers with National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Employee Induction Check, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Careers With National Biscuit Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: Plan Of Organization Personnel Relations Department, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Nabisco Suggestion System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Suggestion System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Nabisco Suggestion System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Suggestion System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Nabisco Suggestion System Manual of Policies and Procedure, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
    March 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 21: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 22: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 23: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 24: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 25: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 26: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 27: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 28: The Bi-Monthly Nabisco Suggestion News Letter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Administrative Organization Chart, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Administrative Organization Chart, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Administrative Organization Chart, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Coat and Suit Survey: women's winter coats, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
    By Dr. Clara H. Friedman. June. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Magnificent Challenge, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Staff Orchestra Quota, Publication (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Labor Savings in American Industry 1899-1939, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Solomon Fabricant. November. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: National Bureau of Economic Research, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: National Bureau of Economic Research, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Liberal Economic Policies, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
    By Alfred Baker Lewis. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: whome?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: That's for me!, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Request For Final Disposition Of Suggestion, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Allen-Wales Add-Venture, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: The United Nations, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Cash Awards for Good Ideas, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: 65th Anniversary, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: The National Cash Register Company and DEFENSE, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: NCR Factory News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: NCR ADD-Venture, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: 1962 Annual Report, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: Cash Awards for Good Ideas, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
    August 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: NCR Factory News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Dayton Daily News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Engineering And Research, Publication (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Home of the world's finest adding machine, Publication (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: New Microfiche Library Materials, Publication (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between The National Cash Register Company And N. C. R. Employees' Independent Union of Dayton, Ohio, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between The National Cash Register Company And N.C.R. Employees' Independent Union of Dayton, Ohio, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between The National Cash Register And N.C.R. Employees' Independent Union of Dayton, Ohio, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between The National Cash Register Company And NCR Employees' Independent Union of Dayton, Ohio, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Agreement Between The National Cash Register Company And NCR Emplooyees' Independent Union of Dayton, Ohio, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Where Will You Work, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: How To Lose Any New Employee, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Working together at NCR, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: working together at NCR, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Scope of the Arbitrator, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Newsletter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Newsletter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Newsletter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Monthly Benefit Statistics, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
    June 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Newsletter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Newsletter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: How do Labor and Schools work together?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Working Together in The National City Bank Of New York and City Bank Farmers Trust Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Executive Council of The National Civic Federation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Public Service Is Your Responsibility, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: A Businessman Looks At Government Pay, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
    By Clarence B. Randall. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Exchange, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Congress Speaks, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: A Brief Summary of the Aims, Purposes and Activities of the National Coal Association, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: 40th Anniversary 1917-1957 "Born Of Necessity, It Has Lived Through Service", Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: NCA its aims organization and activities, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: Crusade for Freedomfrom unfair foreign competition, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 6: An Economic Pattern For Coal, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
    By L.C. Campbell. October 19-21. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Nationalat work for Bituminous Coal Since 1917, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: USA/NCA 1917-1967 Five Decades of Challenge, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Wage Conference Held Brief Session This Afternoon - Then Recessed By Action Of Operators "Until Some Later Development May Give Cuase To Hope Agreeement Can Be Negotiated", Publication (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: National Coat And Suit Industry Recovery Board, Publication (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: National Coat And Suit Industry Recovery Board, Publication (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: The Women's Coat And Suit Industry In 1965, Publication (Box 38, Folder 38)
    By Clara H. Friedman. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: National Coat And Suit Industry Recovery Board, Publication (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Civilian Nuclear Power, Publication (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Research Must Meet The Demand For Clean Air And Abundant Fuels, Publication (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: Newsletter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 39)
    December 18. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: I'm Coal, Man! Do You Dig Me, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: Coal America's Primary Energy Fuel, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: The Impact Of Coal, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: The Impact Of Coal, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 5: The National Coal Policy Conference, Inc., Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 6: Statement By Howard E. Simpson President Baltimore & Ohio Railway Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 7: National Coal Policy Conference, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 8: The Case For A National Fuels Policy Study, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 9: Statement By George H. Love Chairman National Coal Policy Conference, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Box: 38, folder: (Box 38, Folder 41)